winprizesonline.com 2006-07-19

# Win Prizes Online

|  |   
---|---  
|  |  |   
---  
  
|  | 

| 

| 

Our Commitment To Privacy   
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.   
  
---|---|---|---  
  
| 

| 

| 

The Information We Collect  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on WinPrizesOnline.com. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Email address  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
| 

| 

| 

The Way We Use Information  
In order to receive information from WinPrizesOnline.com, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user gives contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest.  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
| 

| 

| 

Our Commitment To Data Security  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Collection of Information by Third Party Sites  
Our site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
|  | 

| 

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.  
  
---|---|---|---
